okay I saw the dam was
by
insurance will pay a premium
using a boost water is possible right
now you know before the press conference
house as well all right
rosco prudential malaysia' comprising
prudential assurance malaysia berhad and
prudential psi hakufu for half his
poverty booths to strengthen and enhance
our offerings in the customer journey or
the highly digitized space to deal build
up with this partnership with booths
Prudential will be able to provide
customers is seamless secure and
convenient experience when it comes to
get insurance premium and hakufu
contribution payments both Prudential
boobs have come together is sharing the
see business goal of making cashless
transactions for consumers as dead in
making Malaysia a future cashless
society this journey started with
Prudential about a year in hot oil but
we received a call of the blue for us to
meet up at the Prudential tea fair you
know back then the congenial to free you
so it was kind of interesting to get a
call Rachel was an area that we was not
thinking of attacking at that point in
time but it was a very very nice
surprise for us to hear that Prudential
had aspirations and intentions to but
the way that their customers make
payments and they were very very much
willing to embrace the catch this
journey that being said I I felt
and I still feel that potential it's a
very special partner because not only
they have that attention but they
actually followed through with it right
I mean what that means is many many
legends a video is talk about more
tetanus but Prudential actually makes
that for me as a concentric company
Prevention's purpose is to help our
customers progress in their lives and
also to meet the evolving needs we live
in a highly digital and very connected
world business smartphone usage in
Malaysia is close to 90% and I
understand that Malaysia's generally
spend almost 14 hours a day
on a variety of digital devices looking
deeper into the figures probably with no
surprise to many of us that this
tech-savvy population Malaysia is led by
urban areas 59% of which aged between of
each less than 25 are using digital
tools in their daily lives innovative
technology and apps clearly grunting our
millennial generation with the excess
information creating instant demands on
their bills health lifestyle and other
daily genes so then the screen and
actually what we want to show you is the
collaboration we use what's possible and
what's happening so here is related the
giant screen and you can see the
vultures insurance and that had happened
and if I were to use the example of
going to insurance so there just click
that and there you go
here's actions of each depicting a
partner like production working the
goose the manager of them at least that
before in the name of custom experience
so for this particular instance when we
really want to get to is a space where
customers are Prudential you are also
those users how can they move into the
ballot where is very convenient for them
to do it several things to ensure that
outside so if you look at the screen
here we've got a number of tau that is
available and they're designed to give
the experience to a potential customer
as well as in this user and if I just
draw attention on something like premium
payment so we click on that really is a
simple page for you to be able to put in
your details to be able to affect the
payment and that's just as simple as
making life easier for customers who
choose different payment option now of
course Prudential really have credit
card as a payment option yeah also auto
deadly who we knew that a lot of
customers of ours are also uses of news
and this is really about availing
another payment channel for for them now
if I go back to the screen that we
already saw and let's take another one
let's see customers that I need to
search for our panel hospital right and
there's a Buddhist team family
this and again here by a bit of a button
you can actually see via map where the
panel hospitals are for electric
customers and again with the living star
service because it's quicker immediate
emergency situation
this is a very much needed convenience
that we provided to our customer
there are other ERISA small and what the
point towards this particular tab which
actually give you access to the powers
by credential application and with a
click of a button if you are really a
registered processor you can get access
to compound snap earlier mr. GaN has
really alluded to the fact that we've
just launched house by Prudential this
is all in one house applications for all
the visions and this is really the space
where they can go in and use some
functionalities that are offered by
powers the months of which is really a
health check that you can actually do a
health assessment through the
application we also have the application
called shadow symptoms which is really
an application where you can ask some
question and then be a dialog powered by
our partner through an AI exchange of
messages the third one is actually the
ability to talk to a doctor virtually
the most obvious
and this is where you can boast of the a
path going into this environment that
you can talk to a doctor both visually
also via or the US wrong and that's just
really a summary of what and there are
others areas were looking at about this
as well in this day in age people are
talking about just a few clicks to get
into the activity that you want to do
and here we also are thinking a little
bit about reading about where you can
just press and that's directly to the
hotline phone for Prudential and that's
really just some functionality that were
putting up as a joint collaboration
without and and this the other towel you
know we're also thinking a lot about
collaborating so there might be some
products that we're looking at in the
future that are only for for this
customer but that will be a subject of
presentation so I just want to say that
this is really what we're thinking of
and the key theme really is is one where
we want to provide convenience to our
customer
what convenience to miss users as well
and that's where I think earlier in the
speeches given by Gary as was mr.
garland we really are talking about
partnering working together we really
just want focus in mind that's what
often consumer or customer for more
organization and I think this is a fine
depiction of really looking at customer
centricity in all ways Tattler ladies
where we're trying to make life easier
for okay because that very generally
follows
[Music]
next up Prudential Insurance Malaysia
Berhad is the guy
you come here for Prudential vs a half
over half
for graduation
[Applause]
[Music]